Guide to the Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF SCRIPTS BY PROGRAM TITLES
  - SHOWER OF STARS
    - Episode #25, undated (Box 339, Folder 5)
  - SID CAESAR INVITES YOU
    See: "Caesar's Hour."
  - SMALL WORLD
    Interviews, with Edward R. Murrow and Fred Friendly. CBS.
    - 1959 Dec 27 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - 1960 Jan 3 (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - 1960 Feb 28 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - 1960 Mar 27 (Box 339, Folder 9)
  - SOUNDSTAGE
    See: "Campbell Soundstage."
  - THE SOUTHERN BAPTIST HOUR
    Religious. NBC.
    Writer: Martin Hoade
    - 1961 Jul 30 (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - 1964 Jan 26 (Box 339, Folder 11)
  - STANLEY
    Situation comedy.
    - 1956 Dec 3 (Box 339, Folder 12)
    - 1956 Dec 24 (Box 339, Folder 13)
    - undated (Box 339, Folder 14)
    - undated (Box 339, Folder 15)
    - undated (Box 339, Folder 16)
  - STAR STAGE
    TV Drama. NBC.
    Producers: Charles Russel
    Directors: Sidney Lumet, S. Mark Smith, Jack Smight, Alan Cooke
    - The Toy Lady Max Watson, 1955 Sep 9 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Cop Without a Badge Joel Carpenter, 1955 Sep 16 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - First Date Doris Frankel, 1955 Sep 30 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - Honest John and the 13 Uncle Sams Joel Carpenter, 1955 Oct 7 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Spring Over Brooklyn George Marrow, 1955 Nov 11 (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - In Houses I Enter Arthur Behrstock, 1955 Nov 18 (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - The Marmalade Scandal George Lowther, 1955 Dec 2 (Box 340, Folder 7)
    - The $1000 Bill Inez Karma, 1955 Dec 9 (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - White Night Robert Wallsten, 1956 Feb 10 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - The School Mistress Saul Levitt, 1956 Feb 17 (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - I am Her Nurse George Bellak, 1956 Mar 2 (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - The Man Who was Irresistible to Women Jackson Stanley, 1956 Mar 16 (Box 340, Folder 12)
    - Scandal on Deepside Kay Arthur, 1956 Mar 30 (Box 340, Folder 13)
    - Being Nice to Emily (2 copies) Richard De Roy, 1956 Apr 13 (Box 340, Folder 14)
    - A Place to be Alone (2 copies) A. J. Russell, 1956 Apr 27 (Box 340, Folder 15)
    - Bend to the Wind George Lowther, 1956 May 4 (Box 340, Folder 16)
    - Foundations George Bellak, 1956 May 25 (Box 340, Folder 17)
    - The Real Thing A. J. Russell, 1956 Jun 1 (Box 340, Folder 18)
  - STAR TONIGHT
    - Episode #5 Zone of Quiet (no author indicated), 1955 Mar 3 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Episode #7 The Murderer (no author indicated), 1955 Mar 17 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - Episode #9 Death of a Stranger Rupert Brooke, 1955 Mar 31 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - The Giants' Stair William Daniel Steele, 1955 Apr 21 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Episode #13 Zero Hour B. Loring, 1955 Apr 28 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - Episode #20 Strength of Steel Rod Serling, 1955 Jun 16 (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - Episode #42 The Cage John De Vries, 1955 Nov 17 (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - Episode #43 Have Faith in Your Agent Judith Parrish, 1955 Nov 24 (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - Episode #44 The Summer Road Ed Moser, 1955 Dec 1 (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - Episode #46 Gang-Up Nicholas E. Baehr, 1955 Dec 15 (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - Episode #47 The Selfish Giant Oscar Wilde, 1955 Dec 22 (Box 341, Folder 11)
    - Episode #51 A Night Visitor Charles Jackson, 1956 Jan 19 (Box 341, Folder 12)
    - Episode #52 Early Frost (no author indicated), 1956 Jan 26 (Box 341, Folder 13)
    - Below Average Nicholas E. Baehr, 1956 Feb 2 (Box 341, Folder 14)
    - Episode #54 The Happy Journey Thornton Wilder, 1956 Feb 9 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Episode #56 Ritual of Innocence Anne Howard Bailey, 1956 Feb 23 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - Episode #57 Three Hours Between Planes Charles Mergendahl (F. Scott Fitzgerald), 1956 Mar 1 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - Episode #58 Night Escape Abby Mann, 1956 Mar 8 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Episode #62 Window on Forever S. Lee Pogostin, 1956 Apr 5 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - Episode #64 An Ambulance for Jill Shirley Wallace, 1956 Apr 19 (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Episode #65 Tough Boy Harry C. Nelson, 1956 Apr 26 (Box 342, Folder 7)
    - Episode #66 Can You Coffeepot on Skates? Nell O'Day Lawrence Williams, 1956 May 3 (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - Episode #67 The Girl Edward Peple, 1956 May 10 (Box 342, Folder 9)
    - Episode #68 A Trip to Czardis Elizabeth and James Hart, 1956 May 17 (Box 342, Folder 10)
    - Episode #70 Kingdom's Child (no author indicated), 1956 May 31 (Box 342, Folder 11)
    - Episode #71 A Small Glass Bottle David Hill, 1956 Jun 7 (Box 342, Folder 12)
    - The Long View Kay Arthur, 1956 Jun 14 (Box 342, Folder 13)
    - Episode #73 The Ascent of P. J. O'Hara Mary Chamberlin Donald Richardson, 1956 Jun 21 (Box 342, Folder 14)
    - Episode #74 Mr. Bell's Creation Stanley Richards, 1956 Jun 28 (Box 342, Folder 15)
    - Shadow of Evil Calvin Tomkins, 1956 Jul 5 (Box 342, Folder 16)
    - The Coffee Shop Incident Howard Garland Sartin, 1956 Jul 12 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Episode #77 The Blood Call (no author indicated), 1956 Jul 19 (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Episode #78 Will Power George Lowther, 1956 Jul 26 (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Episode #79 The Gentleman Caller Robert J. Shaw, 1956 Aug 2 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Episode #80 The Mirthmakers Robert Higgins, 1956 Aug 9 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - A Door You Can Close Michelle Cousin, undated (Box 343, Folder 6)
  - STEVE ALLEN PLYMOUTH SHOW
    See: following Steve Allen Show
  - THE STEVE ALLEN SHOW
    Producer: William O. Harbach
    Directors: Dwight A. Hemion, James Elson
    Writers: Stan Burns, Larry Klein, Herb Sargent, Arne Sultan, Bill Dana, Marvin Worth, Don Hinkley, Frank Peppiatt, Hal Goodman
    - 1956 Jul 22 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - 1956 Jul 29 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - 1956 Aug 5 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - 1956 Aug 26 (Box 343, Folder 10)
    - 1956 Sep 2 (Box 343, Folder 11)
    - 1956 Sep 15 (Box 343, Folder 12)
    - 1956 Sep 23 (Box 343, Folder 13)
    - 1956 Sep 30 (Box 343, Folder 14)
    - 1956 Oct 7 (Box 343, Folder 15)
    - 1956 Oct 14 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - 1956 Oct 21 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - 1956 Nov 18 (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - 1956 Dec 23 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - 1957 Jan 13 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - 1957 Jan 20 (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - 1957 Feb 10 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - 1957 Feb 17 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - 1957 Feb 24 (Box 344, Folder 9)
    - 1957 Mar 3 (Box 344, Folder 10)
    - 1957 Mar 10 (Box 344, Folder 11)
    - 1957 Apr 7 (Box 344, Folder 12)
    - 1957 Apr 14 (Box 344, Folder 13)
    - 1957 Apr 21 (Box 344, Folder 14)
    - 1957 May 5 (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - 1957 May 12 (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - 1957 May 19 (Box 345, Folder 3)
    - 1957 Jun 2 (Box 345, Folder 4)
    - 1957 Jun 9 (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - 1957 Jun 16 (Box 345, Folder 6)
    - 1957 Jun 23 (Box 345, Folder 7)
    - 1957 Jul 7 (Box 345, Folder 8)
    - 1957 Jul 21 (Box 345, Folder 9)
    - 1957 Aug 4 (Box 345, Folder 10)
    - 1957 Aug 11 (Box 345, Folder 11)
    - 1957 Aug 18 (2 copies) (Box 345, Folder 12)
    - 1957 Aug 25 (2 copies) (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - 1957 Sep 8 (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - 1957 Sep 15 (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - 1957 Sep 29 (2 copies) (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - 1957 Oct 6 (3 copies) (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - 1957 Oct 13 (Box 346, Folder 6)
    - 1957 Oct 20 (Box 346, Folder 7)
    - 1957 Oct 27 (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - 1957 Nov 3 (2 copies) (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - 1957 Nov 17 (2 copies) (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - 1957 Nov 24 (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - 1957 Dec 8 (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - 1957 Dec 15 (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - 1957 Dec 22 (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - 1957 Dec 29 (Box 347, Folder 8)
    - 1958 Jan 5 (Box 347, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Jan 26 (Box 347, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Feb 2 (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - 1958 Mar 2 (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - 1958 Apr 6 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - 1958 May 25 (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - 1958 Jun 1 (Box 348, Folder 5)
    - 1958 Jun 15 (Box 348, Folder 6)
    - 1958 Jun 22 (2 copies) (Box 348, Folder 7)
    - 1958 Jun 29 (Box 348, Folder 8)
    - 1958 Jul 6 (Box 348, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Sep14 (Box 348, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Oct 12 (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - 1958 Oct 19 (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - 1958 Oct 26 (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - 1958 Nov 9 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - 1958 Nov 16 (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - 1958 Nov 23 (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - 1958 Nov 30 (Box 349, Folder 7)
    - 1958 Dec 7 (Box 349, Folder 8)
    - 1958 Dec 28 (Box 349, Folder 9)
    - 1959 Jan 18 (Box 349, Folder 10)
    - 1959 Jan 25 (Box 349, Folder 11)
    - 1959 Feb 1 (Box 349, Folder 12)
    - 1959 Feb 8 (Box 349, Folder 13)
    - 1959 Feb 22 (Box 349, Folder 14)
    - 1959 Mar 1 (Box 350, Folder 1)
    - 1959 Mar 15 (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - 1959 Mar 22 (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - 1959 May 17 (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - 1959 May 31 (Box 350, Folder 5)
    - 1959 Jun 7 (Box 350, Folder 6)
    - fragment (Box 350, Folder 7)
  - THE STEVE ALLEN PLYMOUTH SHOW
    - 1960 Feb 22 (Box 350, Folder 8)
  - STEVE LAWRENCE-EYDIE GORME
    Director: Dwight Hemion
    Writers: Johnny Bradford, Bill Dana, Frank Peppiatt, Jud Holstein
    - 1958 Jul 27 (Box 350, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Aug 3 (Box 350, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Aug 10 (2 copies) (Box 350, Folder 11)
    - 1958 Aug 17 (Box 350, Folder 12)
    - 1958 Aug 31 (Box 350, Folder 13)
  - THE STRANGER
  - STRIKE IT RICH
    Game show, CBS.
    Producer: Walt Framer
    - 1954 Oct 6 (Box 350, Folder 14)
  - STUDIO ONE
    Includes "Westinghouse Studio One" and "Studio One Summer Theater."
    Producers: Felix Jackson
    Directors: Franklin Shaffner, Fletcher Markle, Paul Nickell, John Haggott, Jim Sheldon, Alex March, Allen Reisner, Gordon Duff, Seymour Robbie, Robert Herridge, Bill Brown, Herbert Brodkin, Tom Donovan, Norman Felton, Robert Mulligan, Peter Kortner, James MacAllen, Eva Wolas, Jack Smight, Anthony Barr, Sidney Lumet, Arthur Penn, Ira Cirker, John Whiting, Matt Harlib, Karl Genus, Frank Satinstein, Mel Ferber, Dan Petrie, James Clark, David Greene, Ted Post, Herbert Hirschman, Don Taylor, Buzz Kulik
    - Runaway A. J. Russell, 1953 Jan 4 (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - King Coffin Wyllis Cooper (Conrad Aiken), 1953 Feb 16 (Box 351, Folder 2)
    - The Show Piece Emerson Crocker (Booth Tarkington), 1953 Feb 23 (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - My Beloved Husband Robert Wallsten, 1953 Mar 2 (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - A Midnight on the 31st of March Robert Anderson, 1953 Mar 31 (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - The Fathers (2 copies) Henry Kane, 1953 Apr 20 (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - Along Came A Spider Stanley Niss, 1953 Apr 27 (Box 351, Folder 7)
    - Birthright Emerson Crocker, 1953 May 4 (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - The Laugh Maker A. J. Russell, 1953 May 18 (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - Fly with the Hawk Stanley Niss, 1953 May 25 (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - Conflict A. J. Russell, 1953 Jun 8 (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - Greed Louis Pelletier Jack Finke, 1953 Jun 22 (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - Beyond Reason Devery Freeman, 1953 Jul 6 (Box 352, Folder 7)
    - Shadow of a Man May Sarton, 1953 Jul 20 (Box 352, Folder 8)
    - The Roman Kid Paul Gallico, 1953 Aug 3 (Box 352, Folder 9)
    - Flowers from a Stranger Jack Finke, 1953 Aug 10 (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - The Gathering Night (Rudyard Kipling), 1953 Aug 24 (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - Letter from Cairo Reginald Rose, 1953 Aug 31 (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - Look Homeward, Hayseed John Ed Pearce, 1953 Sep 7 (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - Hound-Dog Man Mel Goldberg, 1953 Sep 28 (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - Silent the Song Tad Mosel (Faith Baldwin), 1953 Oct 5 (Box 353, Folder 6)
    - Music and Mrs. Pratt Harry W. Junkin, 1953 Oct 12 (Box 353, Folder 7)
    - Letter of Love Sylvia Berger, 1953 Oct 19 (Box 353, Folder 8)
    - Another Caesar Michael Dyne, 1953 Oct 26 (Box 353, Folder 9)
    - Crime at Blossoms Jerome Ross, 1953 Nov 2 (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - A Bargain with God Howard Rodman, 1953 Nov 16 (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - Confessions of a Nervous Man George Axelrod, 1953 Nov 30 (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - Dry Run David Shaw, 1953 Dec 7 (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - All My Love Mel Goldberg, 1953 Dec 14 (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - Cinderella '53 Arnold Schulman (Cole Porter), 1953 Dec 21 (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - The Remarkable Incident at Carson Corners Reginald Rose, 1954 Jan 11 (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - A Criminal Design A. J. Russell, 1954 Jan 18 (Box 354, Folder 8)
    - A Favor from a Friend Alvin Sapinsley, 1954 Jan 25 (Box 354, Folder 9)
    - Herman Came by Bomber Rod Serling, 1954 Feb 1 (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - Man of Extinction Mel Goldberg, 1954 Feb 8 (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - Dark Possession Gore Vidal, 1954 Feb 15 (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - The Role of Lover Alvin Yudkoff, 1954 Feb 22 (Box 355, Folder 4)
    - Side Street Norman Lessing, 1954 Mar 1 (Box 355, Folder 5)
    - Beyond a Reasonable Doubt Henry Misrock, 1954 Mar 8 (Box 355, Folder 6)
    - Thunder on Sycamore Street Reginald Rose, 1954 Mar 15 (Box 355, Folder 7)
    - Paul's Apartment Robert Wallsten, 1954 Mar 29 (Box 355, Folder 8)
    - Stirmugs Robert R. Presnell, 1954 Apr 5 (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - Jack Sparling, 46 Harry W. Junkin, 1954 Apr 12 (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - Cardinal Mindszenty William Templeton, 1954 May 3 (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - Fear is no Stranger Henry Misrock, 1954 May 10 (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - Castle in Spain Sylvia Weld, 1954 May 17 (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - A Guest at the Embassy Jerome Ross, 1954 Jul 12 (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - The Magic Monday Harry W. Junkin, 1954 Aug 2 (Box 356, Folder 7)
    - Experiment Perilous Mel Goldberg, 1954 Aug 23 (Box 356, Folder 8)
    - The Secret Self Michael Dyne, 1954 Aug 30 (Box 356, Folder 9)
    - U. F. O. Rod Serling, 1954 Sep 6 (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - The Cliff Michael Dyne, 1954 Sep 13 (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - Twelve Angry Men Reginald Rose, 1954 Sep 20 (Box 357, Folder 3)
    - The Boy Who Changed the World Joseph Schrank, 1954 Oct 18 (Box 357, Folder 4)
    - Fatal in My Fashion A. J. Russell, 1954 Oct 25 (Box 357, Folder 5)
    - The Man Who Owned the Town David P. Harmon, 1954 Nov 1 (Box 357, Folder 6)
    - Let Me Go, Lover Henry Misrock, 1954 Nov 15 (Box 357, Folder 7)
    - 12:32 A. M. (2 copies) Reginald Rose, 1954 Dec 13 (Box 357, Folder 8)
    - Two Little Minks Michael Dyne, 1954 Dec 30 (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - The Silent Women Marc Brandel, 1955 Jan 31 (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - Donovan's Brain William Templeton, 1955 Feb 28 (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - Millions of George Joe Masteroff, 1955 Mar 7 (Box 358, Folder 4)
    - The Conviction of Peter Shea Harry W. Junkin, 1955 Mar 14 (Box 358, Folder 5)
    - Dominique Ernest Kinoy, 1955 Mar 28 (Box 358, Folder 6)
    - Cross My Heart Harry W. Junkin, 1955 Apr 4 (Box 358, Folder 7)
    - Summer Pavilion Gore Vidal, 1955 May 2 (Box 358, Folder 8)
    - Strange Companion Don Ettlinger (Christopher Isherwood), 1955 May 16 (Box 358, Folder 9)
    - Pigeons and People (2 copies) Joseph Schrank (George M. Cohan), 1955 May 23 (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Operation Home William M. Altman, 1955 May 30 (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - The Spangers James Yaffe, 1955 Jun 6 (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - The Incredible World of Horace Ford (2 copies) Reginald Rose, 1955 Jun 13 (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - Heart Song Charles S. Gardner, 1955 Jun 20 (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - For the Defense George Bellak, 1955 Jun 27 (Box 359, Folder 6)
    - The Day Before the Wedding Anthony Spinner, 1955 Jul 4 (Box 359, Folder 7)
    - Sane as a Hatter Michael Dyne, 1955 Jul 11 (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - A Terrible Day Carey Wilber, 1955 Jul 18 (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - A Tall Dark Stranger Peter Barry, 1955 Jul 25 (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - Julius Caesar Leo Penn, 1955 Aug 1 (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - The Secret (no author indicated), 1955 Aug 15 (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - The Voysey Inheritance Michael Dyne (Granville Barker), 1955 Aug 22 (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - Mama's Boy Mel Goldberg, 1955 Sep 5 (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - The Pit Charles S. Gardner, 1955 Sep 12 (Box 360, Folder 8)
    - Like Father, Like Son Kathleen and Robert Howard Lindsay, 1955 Sep 19 (Box 360, Folder 9)
    - Three Empty Rooms Reginald Rose, 1955 Sep 26 (Box 360, Folder 10)
    - A Likely Story Frank D. Gilroy, 1955 Oct 3 (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - Uncle Ed and Circumstance Frank Gilroy (Jackie Gleason), 1955 Oct 10 (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - A Most Contagious Game Don Ettlinger, 1955 Oct 17 (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - Private History Jerome Ross, 1955 Oct 24 (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - Split Level Joel Hammil, 1955 Oct 31 (Box 361, Folder 5)
    - Shakedown Cruise Loring D. Mandel, 1955 Nov 7 (Box 361, Folder 6)
    - Julie David Davidson, 1955 Nov 21 (Box 361, Folder 7)
    - The Man Who Caught the Ball at Coogan's Bluff Rod Serling, 1955 Nov 28 (Box 361, Folder 8)
    - The Strongbox William Templeton, 1955 Dec 12 (Box 361, Folder 9)
    - Dino Reginald Rose, 1956 Jan 2 (Box 361, Folder 10)
    - The Talented Mr. Ripley Marc Brandel, 1956 Jan 9 (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - The Bounty Hunters Carey Wilber, 1956 Jan 16 (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - My Son, Johnny Kathleen and Robert Howard Lindsay, 1956 Jan 30 (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - The Silent Gun Carson A. Wiley, 1956 Feb 6 (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - Manhattan Duet Helen Cotton, 1956 Feb 13 (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - Circle of Guilt Mel Goldberg, 1956 Feb 20 (Box 362, Folder 6)
    - Always Welcome Peggy Phillips, 1956 Feb 27 (Box 362, Folder 7)
    - Flower of Pride Michael Dyne, 1956 Mar 12 (Box 362, Folder 8)
    - The Laughter of Giants Paul Crabtree, 1956 Mar 19 (Box 362, Folder 9)
    - This Will Do Nicely L. D. Mandel, 1956 Apr 2 (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - The Arena Rod Serling, 1956 Apr 9 (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - Regarding File #4356 George Bellak, 1956 Apr 16 (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - The Drop of a Hat (2 copies) Dick Berg, 1956 May 7 (Box 363, Folder 4)
    - The Genie of Sutton Place Kenneth Heuer George Selden, 1956 May 14 (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - Family Protection Palmer Thompson, 1956 May 28 (Box 363, Folder 6)
    - The Power William M. Altman, 1956 Jun 4 (Box 363, Folder 7)
    - Mr. Arcularis Conrad Aiken, 1956 Jun 25 (Box 363, Folder 8)
    - The Luck of Luke McTrigger Leo Brady, 1956 Jul 2 (Box 364, Folder 1)
    - Song for A Summer Night Charles Garment, 1956 Jul 9 (Box 364, Folder 2)
    - Emmaline Richard DeRoy, 1956 Jul 16 (Box 364, Folder 3)
    - An Incident of Love William T. Bode, 1956 Jul 23 (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - Something Ventured Jay Glanzrock, 1956 Aug 6 (Box 364, Folder 5)
    - A Day Before Battle Sherman Yellen Peter Stone, 1956 Sep 3 (Box 364, Folder 6)
    - The Cauliflower Heart S. Lee Pogostin, 1956 Sep 10 (Box 364, Folder 7)
    - Dark Morning Arden Casey, 1956 Sep 17 (Box 364, Folder 8)
    - A Special Announcement David Aldrich Peper van Slingerland, 1956 Sep 24 (Box 364, Folder 9)
    - A Man's World Howard Rodman, 1956 Oct 1 (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - The Pilot (2 copies) Paul Crabtree, 1956 Oct 8 (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - The Crimes of Peter Pages Kathleen and Robert Howard Lindsay, 1956 Oct 22 (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - A Christmas Surprise Paul Crabtree, 1956 Dec 24 (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - Goodbye Picadilly Marc Brandel (J. P. Marquand), 1956 Dec 31 (Box 365, Folder 5)
    - Love at Fourth Sight Sumner Locke Elliott, 1957 Jan 7 (Box 365, Folder 6)
    - The Dark Corner Art Wallace, 1957 Jan 14 (Box 365, Folder 7)
    - Dead of Noon Carson Wiley, 1957 Jan 28 (Box 365, Folder 8)
    - Tale of the Comet Robert Alan Aurthur, 1957 Feb 4 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - A Walk in the Forest Howard Rodman, 1957 Feb 11 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - The Defender Reginald Rose, 1957 Feb 25 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - A Child is Waiting Abby Mann, 1957 Mar 11 (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - Walk Down the Hill Ernest Kinoy, 1957 Mar 18 (Box 366, Folder 5)
    - A Member of the Family Horton Foote, 1957 Mar 25 (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - The Rice Sprout Song Loring Mandel, 1957 Apr 15 (Box 366, Folder 7)
    - The Traveling Lady Horton Foote, 1957 Apr 22 (Box 366, Folder 8)
    - Eight Feet to Midnight Marc Brandel, 1957 Apr 29 (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - The Out-of-Towners Tad Mosel, 1957 May 6 (Box 367, Folder 2)
    - The Man Who Wasn't Himself Howard Rodman, 1957 May 20 (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - The Furlough (2 copies) Richard Fielder, 1957 Jun 3 (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - The Staring Match Jerry McNeeley, 1957 Jun 17 (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - Good-Will Ambassador (2 copies) Jerome Ross, 1957 Jun 24 (Box 367, Folder 6)
    - Love Me to Pieces Romeo Muller, 1957 Jul 15 (Box 367, Folder 7)
    - My Mother and How She Undid Me Theodore Apstein, 1957 Aug 5 (Box 367, Folder 8)
    - The Unmentionable Blues Helen Cotton, 1957 Aug 12 (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - Mutiny on the Shark Part I Max Ehrlich, 1957 Sep 23 (Box 368, Folder 2)
    - Mutiny on the Shark Part II Max Ehrlich, 1957 Sep 30 (Box 368, Folder 3)
    - The Morning Face Tad Mosel, 1957 Oct 7 (Box 368, Folder 4)
    - Please Report Any Odd Characters Jerome Ross, 1957 Nov 18 (Box 368, Folder 5)
    - Escape Route William Mourne, 1957 Dec 2 (Box 368, Folder 6)
    - No Deadly Medicine Part I Arthur Hailey, 1957 Dec 9 (Box 368, Folder 7)
    - No Deadly Medicine Part II Arthur Hailey, 1957 Dec 16 (Box 368, Folder 8)
    - Brotherhood of the Bell Dale Wasserman David Karp, 1958 Jan 6 (Box 368, Folder 9)
    - Trial by Slander Roger O. Hirson, 1958 Jan 20 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - Tide of Corruption Marc Brandel, 1958 Feb 17 (Box 369, Folder 2)
    - The Fair-Haired Boy Herman Raucher, 1958 Mar 3 (Box 369, Folder 3)
    - Edge of Truth Adrian Spies, 1958 Apr 28 (Box 369, Folder 4)
    - The McTaggart Succession John McGreevey, 1958 May 5 (Box 369, Folder 5)
    - The Enemy Within Richard DeRoy, 1958 May 16 (Box 369, Folder 6)
    - The Left-Handed Welcome Robert Presnell, Jr., 1958 Jun 16 (Box 369, Folder 7)
    - The Undiscovered Joseph Landon, 1958 Jun 30 (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - The Last Summer Frank D. Gilroy, 1958 Aug 4 (Box 370, Folder 2)
    - Tagalong Ernest Kinoy, 1958 Aug 11 (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Birthday Present Jack Roche, 1958 Aug 18 (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - No Place to Run James P. Cavanagh, 1958 Sep 15 (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - Image of Fear James P. Cavanagh, 1958 Sep 29 (Box 370, Folder 6)
    - Miss Turner's Decision Howard Rodman, undated (Box 370, Folder 7)
    - The Temptation of Harry Ashcroft James Blumgarten, undated (Box 370, Folder 8)
    - Peacock City Carey Wilber, undated (Box 370, Folder 9)
    - Doll Face Jerome Ross, undated (Box 370, Folder 10)
    - The Master of the Rose Michael Dyne, undated (Box 371, Folder 1)
    - The Black Sheep Brainerd Duffield, undated (Box 371, Folder 2)
    - Guitar Harvey Miller, undated (Box 371, Folder 3)
    - The Bend in the Road John Vlahos, undated (Box 371, Folder 4)
    - The Years In Between Will Schneider Herman Goldberg, undated (Box 371, Folder 5)
    - The Hollywood Complex John Vlahos, undated (Box 371, Folder 6)
    - The Deaf Heart Mayo Simon, undated (Box 371, Folder 7)
    - Death and Taxes Laurence Marks, undated (Box 371, Folder 8)
    - Snap Your Fingers Richard DeRoy, undated (Box 371, Folder 9)
    - Flight Robert Herridge (John Steinbeck), undated (Box 372, Folder 1)
    - End of Her Honeymoon Raphael Hayes, undated (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - Rudy Dan Clabrese, undated (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - The Grown Ones Arthur Rodney Coneybeare, undated (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - The King in Yellow Raymond Chandler, undated (Box 372, Folder 5)
    - (no title page) (Box 372, Folder 6)
  - SUNDAY GALLERY
    Political documentary.
    Producer: Bill Osterhaus
    Director: Dan Peters
    - 1960 Jun 5 (Box 372, Folder 7)
    - 1960 Oct 23 (Box 372, Folder 8)
    - undated (Box 372, Folder 9)
  - SUNDAY SHOWCASE
    Biographical drama.
    - The Margaret Bourke-White Story Joseph Liss, 1960 Jan 3 (Box 372, Folder 10)
  - SUSPENSE
    Producers: Martin Manulis
    Directors: Robert Milligan, David Heilweil, Byron Paul